Can I talk to you, brother?
Where is your mum?
Take care of your mum.
Okay?
Okay.
Take care of your mum.
Thank you, sir.
Your mum is a good woman.
I don't know why they call her all (kind of) names.
They called her a witch. There is nothing they have not called this woman.
Yes, sir.
Thank You, Jesus!
Why do you people believe this woman is a witch?
That is what the people are calling her.
Even my dad's family, all of them call her a witch.
That is my family on my father's side called my mother a witch.
This is the problem you people have, calling an innocent person - 'a nature of God' -
someone who is not a witch witch.
This woman has cried and cried.
Exactly, sir.
None of you will prosper unless this woman accepts sorry
and the Spirit of God forgives you.
This woman suffered.
You are going to bring this woman.
Okay? Go and wait for me.
Thank you, sir.
It will not only be you.
We will beg mama with the Spirit of God and she will accept.
All of the family will be delivered.
They have cursed this woman.
Because of that, she is living at the backyard of the house.
Yes, sir.
My name is Charles Benson.
I'm from Delta State.
The woman standing beside me is my mother whom we called a witch.
These people behind me are my brothers and sisters.
This other mama here is my mother-in-law.
Last Sunday, when we were in the first service, the man of God called me.
He asked me where my mother was.
I said that my mother was at home.
He then said that I should take care of her.
I said, "Okay, sir".
After that, he prophesied to me.
He asked, "Why do they call your mother all sorts of names?"
"They call her a witch. She is not a witch; she is innocent."
He said that even I called her a witch.
He said that because of that, she cried.
Because of her crying, there is no breakthrough in the family.
So, he said I should bring her here.
That is why I brought her here with my family.
What the man of God said is true.
We called her a witch and put her at the backyard.
My name is Fatima.
When my husband died, the family called me to their meeting.
They asked me what happened.
I told them that I didn't know what killed their brother.
They said that I was the one that killed my husband.
I said that I didn't know anything concerning that,
that he was sick.
After we came from the village,
the house that my children, my husband and I were staying in,
my husband's family drove me out.
I begged that they should let me and my children stay.
They said that they had already shared the house and given it to someone else.
They threw my property outside and drove me away.
I had nowhere to stay and even to eat was difficult.
This mama saw me suffering when all my property was outside.
She met me and said she couldn't leave me like that.
She took some of the property and took it to the backyard where she used to work.
It was a backyard, outside.
They gave me money to live and cook.
We quite understand what has happened to you - the pain.
That was why we invited you here today
to let the world know that you are not a witch
and that we are very sorry for what happened.
This is a glorious day for every one of us.
We are very sorry; mama is not a witch.
Son, please be on your knee and hug your mum.
So, please, mama, pray for them.
Mama is praying for them.
So, please, as you are offering this prayer, the Lord Almighty is praying for them as well.
They are looking for breakthrough
and they don't know the sin they have committed, ignorantly.
Now, mama has forgiven them.
Mama, you should forgive everyone.
All these are my husband's family.
The last son threw my things away.
So, you threw away mama's things?
It was due to permission from the home, sir.
He needs prayer.
He needs prayer because he didn't know what he was doing.
He threw all my property away.
He is the one that threw your property away?
Yes.
That was the order from the home.
That was why mama said you need prayer.
Mama knows that you acted ignorantly.
She said that they drove this woman outside.
She was the one taking care of her.
Nobody from the family asked about her or the children,
how they were feeding and how they were doing.
So, it is over now. We thank God.
God is the one who gave us this revelation
and the same God is saying, "It is over".
Man of God, I forgive all the people who made me suffer.
Family Reconciled in Jesus' Name
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.